education.weebly.com 2017-07-04

# Weebly Website Builder: Create a Free Website, Store or Blog

### Last updated September 23, 2016

### 1\. What This Privacy Notice Covers

This notice covers how Weebly, Inc., a U.S. company ("Weebly," "we," "us," or "our") treats personal information that it collects and receives from its website (www.weebly.com), website hosting and design services, communication tools, mobile applications, app marketplace, ecommerce tools, and other services (collectively, the “Service”).

We are not in the business of selling personal information about you. We use information shared with us for the purpose of running and improving our Service and in that capacity will operate as a data controller and, to the extent we process data, a data processor.

This notice tells you what information we collect, steps we take to protect and secure it, how we use and share information, and finally, how you can contact us with questions or concerns.

### 2\. Information We Collect

**(a) Personal Information.**  We collect personal information (e.g., name, email address, phone number, etc.) when you:

  * register an account with us;
  * contact our customer support services;
  * sign-up as, or are invited to be, a member of a Pro or Business account user’s site;
  * are referred to us through our “invite a friend” referral feature;
  * enter our promotions, contests, or sweepstakes;
  * post content on a Weebly website or blog;
  * sign-up to be an App Developer; and
  * post an App review in our App Marketplace

**(b) Other User Information.**  When you access and use our Service, we automatically collect and store in log files your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, and other user information as part of our Service analytics (individually and collectively, “Automatically Collected Information”) to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the Service. We use mobile application platform permissions when collecting other information from you. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

**(c) Billing Information.**  If you sign up for a Weebly Starter, Pro, or Business account, register a domain through us, or purchase another paid service, we require your billing information in order to process the transaction. Billing information includes your name, address, telephone number, credit card details, PayPal email address, and other information necessary to process the transaction.

We will retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number, credit card type, name, address, and some other billing information, so that you may identify that card used in the future. Weebly does not store your full credit card number or CVV2; this information is discarded after your transaction has been processed.

If your subscription is auto-renewing, our authorized payment processor will store your payment information on their secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription.

All transactions are processed over an industry standard SSL/TLS connection, with a minimum of 128-bit encryption.

**(d) Cookies and Tracking Technologies.**  Weebly and our affiliates, partners, and service providers (such as marketing, analytics, and customer support partners) use cookies and similar technologies for analyzing trends, site administration, tracking mobile application installations, and understanding how users interface with our site(s), and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and in an aggregated basis.

**VISITING WEEBLY WITH YOUR BROWSER SET TO ACCEPT COOKIES OR USING OUR MOBILE APPLICATIONS OR OTHER SOFTWARE TELLS US YOU WANT TO USE OUR SERVICE AND YOU CONSENT TO OUR USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES TO PROVIDE YOU OUR SERVICE.**

We use cookies for a number of purposes, some of which are strictly necessary, including but not limited to our shopping cart, to remember user settings such as language preferences, and for authentication.  **You can control the use of certain cookies at the individual browser level or in your operating system preferences**. If you opt-out of such cookies, you may still use our Service, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Service may be limited.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Service or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on our Service and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).

**If you are located in Europe, for more information about targeted advertising or to opt out of having your browser information used for these purposes, please  [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or change your cookie preferences on your browser or device settings. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.**

**(e) Third Party Analytics Services.**  Some parts of our Service use third party analytic services to help us create a better user experience.

  * Flurry. You can opt-out of Flurry’s mobile analytics service at [Flurry Opt-Out](http://www.flurry.com/legal-privacy/end-user-opt-out). The opt-out is specific to Flurry activities and does not affect the activities of other ad networks or analytics providers we may use. When you opt-out, Flurry will stop tracking data for the device identified by the provided MAC address and/or device identifier going forward and Flurry analytics tracking will stop across all applications within the Flurry network. 
  * Google. For the web, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) and install the add-on for your specific browser. For our mobile applications, you can opt-out using our “Privacy Opt-Out” settings within our applications. 
  * Google Tag Manager. You can opt-out of Google Tag Manager’s mobile service by using our “Privacy Opt-Out” settings within our applications. 

**(f) Do Not Track.**  Currently, we do not support Do Not Track or “DNT.” DNT is a preference you set in your web browser to tell visited websites you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable DNT through the preferences or settings of your web browser.

**(g) Mobile App.** When you download and use the Service through our mobile app, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID"). 

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of the Service on your device. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, content, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from.

We may also send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about events or promotions. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure that you receive proper notifications, we need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

### 3\. Legal Ability to Enter Into Contracts

You are prohibited from creating or using a Weebly account if you are not legally capable of entering into contracts, for example, if you are not the age of majority in your country or region. If you are not the age of majority in your country or region, you may only create or use a Weebly account with the supervision and consent of a parent or guardian or alternatively through a special student account created by a teacher through [education.weebly.com](http://education.weebly.com/), provided the teacher has obtained signed consent from your parent or guardian.

### 4\. Information Use, Sharing, Disclosure, and Retention

**(a) Use.**  Weebly uses information for providing products and services, identification and authentication, Service operation, analytics and improvements, support, contact (e.g., sending notifications related to use of the Service), research, and anonymous reporting. We may combine Automatically Collected Information with other information we collect about you to improve site functionality and the services we offer you, and for Service and internal marketing analytics.

IP addresses, browser and session information may be used to:

  * Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP. 
  * Estimate the total number of users from specific geographical regions using the Service.
  * Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services, or resources that we offer. 
  * Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse.

_Marketing Emails_. When you sign-up for our Service, you may choose to agree to receive marketing communications from us. To the extent you have not already done so during sign-up, you may select not to receive from Weebly or any of our partners certain emails related to marketing, promotions, sweepstakes, contests, or newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by [unsubscribing here](http://www.weebly.com/weebly/unsubscribe.php).

_User Site Membership/Registration_. When you register, or are invited to register, as a member of a website operated by one of our Pro or Business account users, we store and use your information solely to provide administrative services in support of our member feature (such as account set-up and password reset). Please contact the site operator directly to have your registration information removed.

_Publicly Accessible Information_. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, like blogs, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To have your personal information removed from our blog or community forum, submit a request through our [help center](http://hc.weebly.com/). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. Please note, standard domain registration shows your personal contact information in the public WHOIS database. You can shield your personal information from public view and help protect yourself against spam, fraud, identity theft, and more by purchasing Private Registration from us.

_Testimonials_. We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [testimonials@weebly.com](mailto:testimonials@weebly.com).

_Referral Opt-Out_. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Service, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Service. Weebly stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may [unsubscribe here](http://www.weebly.com/weebly/unsubscribe.php) to request we remove this information from our database.

**(b) Sharing.**  Weebly does not share personal information we learn about you from your use of the Service with others except as described in this notice.

Weebly may share your personal information where it is necessary to complete a transaction, to operate or improve the Service, to detect fraud or compliance with export regulations, or to do something that you have asked us to do. We use other third parties such as payment processors to bill you for goods and services. These third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us and are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.

From time to time, Weebly or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake, or contest on Weebly. You may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address, or home address, or to answer questions in order to participate. This information will be used strictly for promotion, sweepstake, or contest administration and fulfillment.

Unless we have your permission, we do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

As we continue to develop our business, we may also buy or sell all or part of our business. In such transactions, personal information you have shared with us is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred. The transferred personal information will remain subject to the promises made in this privacy notice or subsequent notices to which you have consented. If Weebly is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**(c) Disclosure.** Weebly may disclose personal information about you under the following circumstances:

  * In certain situations, Weebly may disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including but not limited to national security or law enforcement requests. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or similar legal processes, to establish or exercise our legal rights or, defend against legal claims, or if in our judgment in such circumstances disclosure is required or appropriate. 
  * If we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our various terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

**(d) Retention.**  We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you the Service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Framework**

Weebly complies with the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from Switzerland. Weebly has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Weebly’s certification, please click [here](https://safeharbor.export.gov/swisslist.aspx). 

**EU - U.S. Privacy Shield**

Weebly participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Weebly is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield List](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

Weebly is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and may subsequently transfer data to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Weebly complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions. By using the service, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Weebly is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

If you still have privacy or data use concerns that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Under certain conditions, as more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### 5\. 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps

Our Service includes various third party features, services, and apps, including but not limited social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, apps you may add to your Site via the App Marketplace, back end service providers, and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Service (“3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps”). These 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the 3rd Party Features and Apps to function properly. 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Service. Your interactions with these 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps may be governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps, and you are responsible for viewing that company’s relevant privacy policy.

3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps may also support functions that require that you disclose certain personal information given your choice of participation. This information is collected in many different ways such as: forms, surveys, contests, forums, subscribing or unsubscribing to mailings and correcting or updating personal information and are only used for the purpose in which they were collected. 3rd Party Features, Services, and Apps that may collect sensitive information, such as financial information (credit card) to process purchases for products or services.

### 6\. Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Service includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

### 7\. Facebook Login; Google +

You can log in to our Service using sign-in services such as Facebook Login, Google+, or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Login give you the option to post information about your activities on our Service to your profile page to share with others within your network. Learn how to control how information is shared on your Google+ profile [here](https://support.google.com/plus/answer/1047279?hl=en).

### 8.Confidentiality and Security

We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

Data transmissions over the Internet are not 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems.

Your account information is password-protected. Additionally, your account's password is stored using a salted, variable work factor, one-way hash algorithm.

In certain areas, Weebly uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions (such as when entering credit card details). However, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of a firewall or secure server software.

If Weebly learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Service or providing personal information to us, you are consenting to Weebly communicating with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues related to your use of the Service. We may post a notice on our applicable web sites if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the applicable web sites. In these circumstances, we may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) submit a request through our [help center](http://hc.weebly.com/).

If you post any comments or content on our Service, any personally identifiable information you choose to provide there may be read, collected, or used by other users of the Service, as well as other parties. Weebly is not responsible for any information you choose to submit in these forums and we cannot guarantee that other users have not made any copies of and/or will not use such information outside of the Service.

### 9\. Changing your Preferences and Personal Information

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold or process your personal information on behalf of third parties. You can access and edit your account information with Weebly at any time by logging into your account. You can also contact us via the [help center](https://hc.weebly.com/hc/en-us), and we will respond as soon as possible, but at most within 30 days.

You can delete your applicable account by visiting the applicable account deletion page; however, some personal information, primarily your contact information, may remain in our records to the extent necessary to protect our legal interests or document compliance with regulatory requirements.

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer wish to use our Service, you may correct, update, or delete such information by making the change on your user account page, or by submitting a request through our [help center](http://hc.weebly.com/).

### 10\. Changes to this Privacy Notice

Weebly reserves the right to revise, modify, or update this notice at any time. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your particular Weebly account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### 11\. Contacting Weebly

If you have a privacy concern regarding Weebly, or this notice, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the Service, you should complete a support request at [http://help.weebly.com](http://help.weebly.com/), or you can write to us by email at [privacy@weebly.com](mailto:privacy@weebly.com?subject=Privacy%20-%20Support%20Request) or by mail at:

Attention: Legal - Privacy  
Weebly, Inc.  
460 Bryant St., #100  
San Francisco, California 94107 USA

### Change Log:

**September 2016:** Changes were made to update this policy in accordance with Privacy Shield and US-Swiss Safe Harbor. Additional disclosures and explanations have also been provided in Sections 1, 2, 4, 9, and 10.
